UTAGE: Formed on an audition show, an idol group
that's currently rising quickly to the top...
UTAGE: F/ACE.
UTAGE: And this is my beloved oshi...
TAMON: What? You're lonely?
TAMON: Then I'll embrace all of you with my song.
TAMON: You better be ready, all my
girlfriends around the country!
TAMON: Let's go!
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: God
UTAGE: Gah! That closeup almost ended me!
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: God
UTAGE: It both added to
and took years off my lifespan!
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: God
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is literally a god!
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: God
SIGN: -kun
SIGN: Tamon-kun
UTAGE DAD: Ef-ace again?
You sure don't get tired of them.
UTAGE MOM: You mean "F/ACE."
UTAGE: Oh, my god, wait! Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait...
UTAGE MOM: It is pretty funny watching our child
lose her mind over her oshi.
HOMARE: Onee-chan's all scary
when she loses her mind, so no.
YAMATO: It's not like you're ever going to meet him,
so you're better off studying.
UTAGE NARRATOR: I'm Utage Kinoshita, age 16.
UTAGE: His expression right
there was literally perfect!
UTAGE NARRATOR: I'm a high school student who survives off
my oshi as my family side-eyes me.
UTAGE: How can you look this cool?!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun saved the world
with just his face again.
UTAGE: Okay, this should do it for the angle.
UTAGE: Perfect.
UTAGE: My oshi is Tamon Fukuhara-kun.
SIGN: You Need Money to Support Your Oshi!
UTAGE: He's the sexy and wild member of F/ACE,
whose handsome face is too OP
UTAGE: and is way too hot
for a high school student.
SIGN: The Reason I Continue to Evolve
Tamon Fukuhara
TAMON: He's continuously giving girls
all across Japan fantasies
TAMON: with his electrifying performances
that put pro dancers to shame.
TAMON: He's eventually going to be arrested
for being-too-hot crimes.
SIGN: 2D F/ACE
SIGN: Tamon Fukuhara
16 YEAR OLD TAMON: I want to make everyone in the world smile.
SIGN: 16 years old,
High School Student
16 YEAR OLD TAMON: I want to make everyone in the world smile.
UTAGE: He was so baby and innocent
at his audition two years ago.
UTAGE: He's grown up so much.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Email
SIGN: F/ACE Dome Concert
Lottery Results Notification
UTAGE: I-It's here!
UTAGE: No, wait. Calm down, me.
UTAGE: F/ACE's first T-Dome concert has 95 applicants
for each ticket. My chances are slim.
UTAGE: No matter the result, I decided
to accept my fate long ago.
UTAGE: Ah!
UTAGE: I got in!
SIGN: Lottery Results
SIGN: Success
SIGN: Ticket Amount
SIGN: 2 Tickets
SIGN: Lottery Results
SIGN: Success
SIGN: Ticket Amount
SIGN: Housekeeping Made Easy
SIGN: Leave it to Us! Housekeeping Service
HOUSEKEEPING PRESIDENT: Sorry about this, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Huh?
HOUSEKEEPING PRESIDENT: I called you in so suddenly on your day off.
UTAGE: Oh, it's fine.
HOUSEKEEPING PRESIDENT: Toda-san ended up
in the hospital with appendicitis,
HOUSEKEEPING PRESIDENT: so you'll be taking care of the housekeeping
at this residence for a while.
SIGN: Kinoshita
UTAGE: Yes, ma'am! Leave it to me.
UTAGE: You need money to
support your oshi!
UTAGE: I started this part-time housekeeping job
because of the great pay and terms,
UTAGE: and now, I've finally got the hang of it.
UTAGE: But this Tamon Fukuhara person
has the same name as Tamon-kun...
SIGN: Customer Registry
Name: Tamon Fukuhara
IMAGINARY TAMON: It's our little secret, my little kitten.
UTAGE: Is it actually him?!
SIGN: Forbidden Garden
UTAGE: Come on, this isn't a self-insert fic!
UTAGE: This is the building, right?
UTAGE: Pardon me.
UTAGE: No way.
UTAGE: While he looks insanely pale,
UTAGE: there's no way I wouldn't recognize the face
that's been burned into my retinas every day.
UTAGE: Fukuhara-sama, I'll be using your vacuum.
TAMON: Oh, sure.
SIGN: Badump
UTAGE: Th... This is...
UTAGE: That time I came to make money to support
my oshi, but it was actually his place!
UTAGE: Pardon me.
UTAGE: Maybe he's just really shy
when he's not working.
UTAGE: Okay, where's this vacuum...
UTAGE: Fukuhara-sama, I'm sorry
to bother you again.
UTAGE: Where do you keep the detergent?
TAMON: N-No one told me someone so young
was going to show up.
UTAGE: I can't go into work mode at home.
What am I going to do?
UTAGE: She totally thought, "Holy crap,
what a totally gloom-and-doom loser.
UTAGE: Get a stinkbug stuck up your nose and die!"
UTAGE: I-I definitely didn't go that far...
TAMON: I'm finished! I'm gonna be exposed!
SIGN: It's been revealed that Tamon Fukuhara
is actually a gloom-and-doom
loser with 0 friends lolololololol
SIGN: lololololololololololol
SIGN: So disappointed
SIGN: Give me back my money
SIGN: Yikes...
SIGN: That's hilarious
SIGN: "Sexy & wild" my ass
SIGN: Pandered to women too much
SIGN: That's hilarious
SIGN: He's a total gloom-and-doom loser
SIGN: lololololololololol
SIGN: Don't try so hard
SIGN: You can always tell when an introvert
SIGN: tries to be
an extrovert
SIGN: Get a stinkbug
stuck up your
nose and die
SIGN: Gimme back my money
TAMON: She's going to make a post about me
with lolololololololololol written on it!
TAMON: I'm gonna be a laughingstock to the world,
TAMON: and all the fans who supported me
will label me a traitor!
SIGN: Traitor
TAMON: I'm gonna get stabbed and bleed out
in some midnight alley.
TAMON: Man, my life was harsh.
TAMON: I should've never been born.
UTAGE: Is this seriously the same person?
UTAGE: Is he really the famous Tamon-kun,
who's known to be the ultimate eye candy?
UTAGE: He does have his first concert at the Dome
coming up, so maybe he's just tired.
UTAGE: What am I going to do
if Tamon-kun retires from anxiety?!
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: He reveals the reason for his
retirement as anxiety
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: BREAKING
NEWS
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: F/ACE's Tamon Fukuhara-san Announced His Retirement
TAMON: Thank you for everything.
UTAGE: Then I'll die!
UTAGE: I can't ever let that happen!
UTAGE: Um, Fukuhara-sama.
UTAGE: I've actually been a huge fan of yours
ever since your audition two years ago.
UTAGE: I probably shouldn't say this while I'm
working right now, but I just have to say it.
UTAGE: I'm so happy that you were born,
UTAGE: and I'm so, so happy
that you became a singer!
UTAGE: I couldn't be happier!
TAMON: I'm so sorry.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: If you're that big a fan,
TAMON: I'm sure seeing the IRL version of me
just shattered your image of me.
TAMON: You must be so hurt.
TAMON: I've been deceiving fans and hurting them,
so I'm just... absolute trash, aren't I?
TAMON: I'm lesser than industrial waste.
UTAGE: You're not deceiving anyone!
TAMON: Honestly, nobody should be
supporting me at all.
TAMON: I'm just a phony.
UTAGE: What? A phony?
RANDO GIRL: Tamon-kun!
RANDO GIRL: I adore you!
SIGN: Congrats on your debut
RANDO GIRL: I love you!
RANDO GIRL: Congrats on your debut!
UTAGE: Fukuhara-sama.
UTAGE: Are you looking down on our love?
UTAGE: You're not a phony.
SIGN: God
SIGN: Tamon-kun
TAMON: Wh-What are you doing?!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is the hottest
and greatest of all time
UTAGE: who turns our world into paradise!
UTAGE: Therefore, he is literally a god!
UTAGE: I don't care if you're broken in the head.
That is the undeniable truth.
SIGN: God
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: Go
SIGN: God
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is a god!
UTAGE: The apostle of love sent to all the maidens!
UTAGE: And an angel! The holy trinity!
UTAGE: Repeat after me! "Tamon-kun is god!"
TAMON: Tamon-kun is god! Wait, what the hell?!
UTAGE: I don't care if you're actually him.
SIGN: Church of Tamon
SIGN: Unconditional
love for
Tamon Fukuhara
UTAGE: Antis won't ever bring me down!
SIGN: Nuisance Otaku
SIGN: Utage
TAMON: Your duality seems even
more intense than mine.
UTAGE: But I must say...
UTAGE: I'm amazed you decided to play that character,
considering your actual personality.
TAMON: Er, yes. That was decided by my agency.
UTAGE: GJ, agency.
TAMON: There's someone I look up to.
TAMON: And it's ridiculous for me to think this...
more like re-die-culous...
TAMON: But I wanted to make
everyone in the world smile,
SIGN: God
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: on-kun
TAMON: just like they did.
SIGN: God
SIGN: kun
UTAGE: That's what he said at the audition...
SIGN: God
TAMON: But nobody can smile seeing a guy
exuding as much doom and gloom as me.
UTAGE: I see.
UTAGE: His character might be an act,
but it's not fake.
UTAGE: His feelings are real.
That's why he resonates with so many people.
SIGN: Voice Training Habits to Refine Your Sound
The Hippo That Makes Dreams Come True
How Nutjobs Think
How Does One Live on Their Own?!
How to See My True Self
Don't Panic Even When You're Stuck
UTAGE: You really are Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: You're not a phony.
PRODUCER SHIRAISHI: Listen up.
PRODUCER SHIRAISHI: We have no need for your true self.
PRODUCER SHIRAISHI: Never let it show.
UTAGE: Fukuhara-san?!
TAMON: I suddenly got really famous...
TAMON: And all kinds of people would
say all kinds of things to me...
TAMON: Despite everything the fans said...
TAMON: I couldn't believe what I wanted to anymore.
TAMON: But I found that version of myself
insanely pathetic and trust myself the least.
TAMON: Maybe I'll go to a jungle, the outback,
TAMON: or a deserted island where no one else lives,
and spend the rest of my days there.
SIGN: Secluded Areas Around the World
UTAGE: You were just talking about your dream,
so how did we end up here?!
UTAGE: If you don't believe me, I'm going to keep
supporting you until you do believe me,
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san and all!
TAMON: Gloomyhara?
MUSHROOM: Gloom.
UTAGE: I will not let him quit!
F/ACE: Eyes on you. We are F/ACE!
F/ACE: Hello, we're F/ACE!
TAMON: I'm the conductor of love and positivity!
TAMON: I'm the sexy and wild member,
Tamon Fukuhara!
OURI: I may be the youngest, but please rely on me.
OURI: I'm the prince of the group, Ouri Sakaguchi.
NATSUKI: Happy, pretty, and everyone's angel!
NATSUKI: I'm Natsuki Ishibashi!
KEITO: I love rice balls! I'm Keito Tachibana.
KEITO: I guess you could call me
the leader of the group.
KEITO: And last but not least...
RINTARO: I'm Kai.
TAMON: And finally, today...
NATSUKI: Finally, finally!
SIGN: Fan Name
KEITO: We'll be deciding on our fan name.
TAMON/NATSUKI: Fasoname!
KEITO: It says fan.
TAMON: Thanks for all the ideas
you gave us, everyone!
TAMON: There were so many names we'd never
think of so our minds were just blown!
think of, so our minds were just blown!
UTAGE: So this... is this.
TAMON: You didn't expose me, did you?
UTAGE: I did not!
SIGN: Ginger
SIGN: Garlic
UTAGE: The last time I peeked into your fridge,
I was so surprised at how little was in there.
UTAGE: And your trash was filled with
instant food containers.
UTAGE: Have you been eating properly?
TAMON: I'm sorry I'm so environmentally unfriendly.
TAMON: I'm sorry that I'm trash producing more trash.
UTAGE: That's not what I'm saying.
UTAGE: I'm just surprised you're able to sing and
dance like that with your current diet.
TAMON: Er, yes. In exchange, I'm unable to
move at all while I'm at home.
UTAGE: As I said, I'll be making you food
from now on as well.
TAMON: I don't really eat other people's homemade food.
UTAGE: My idol was extremely malnourished.
UTAGE: Food greatly affects your mental health!
UTAGE: Please have a taste.
UTAGE: I made it wearing gloves and a mask,
so it'd be just like eating at a restaurant.
SIGN: Om
UTAGE: You fraud.
UTAGE: I can't allow you to starve, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Here you go.
SIGN: Om...
UTAGE: T-Tamon-kun?!
TAMON: Oh, man.
TAMON: That's definitely my type.
UTAGE: Huh? Wha? Huh? Wh-Wh-What?!
SIGN: *He's talking about the fried chicken
TAMON: Hey... Can I eat you all up right now?
SIGN: *Again, he's talking about the fried chicken
UTAGE: Tamon-kun...
UTAGE: Here lies Utage Kinoshita, age sixteen.
UTAGE: Her cause of death...
Tamon-kun was too sexy.
SIGN: Utage Kinoshita
MUSHROOM: Gloom.
TAMON: Th-That startled me...
UTAGE: Huh? That's my line!
I literally was about to perish.
UTAGE: You didn't mention that you'd
suddenly flip over to work mode!
TAMON: I-I'm sorry.
TAMON: I've been so busy lately that
my on and off switch seems a bit buggy.
TAMON: Man, my face hurts...
My muscles are twitching...
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san?! Are you okay?!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san!
UTAGE: Becoming the ideal idol to your fans...
UTAGE: That must be so difficult.
UTAGE: But you still push through.
UTAGE: You work hard because you
want to see everyone smile.
SIGN: Tuna
UTAGE: I guess I'll make spring rolls for dinner.
MC: T-Tamon-kun?
TAMON: Huh?
MC: You're exuding your pheromones
way more than usual today.
MC: What do you eat to exude so much?
TAMON: I recently had some canned tuna
spring rolls that were really good.
TAMON: Oh, and ginger pork!
UTAGE: Wait, that's my recipe.
TAMON: Eating good food just
gives you endless strength.
MC: What a safe answer for an 18 year old.
MC: All right, let's have
F/ACE get ready to perform.
F/ACE: Right!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Yes, what is it?
TAMON: I was told to take a selfie
at home for the fan club.
UTAGE: A candid shot of Tamon-kun at home?!
TAMON: But I just can't get into work mode
at home... What should I do?
UTAGE: We must not let these photos
out into the world.
UTAGE: Well...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is a fan service
machine that never misses,
SIGN: Smooch
UTAGE: and he can't help but do
what fan signs ask him to.
SIGN: Do the Soran Bushi
UTAGE: There are times he gets played,
UTAGE: but he's a forgiving god that does
what's requested of him anyway.
SIGN: Do a triple axel
UTAGE: The end.
UTAGE: Which means...
SIGN: Flip on that switch
TAMON: I've locked onto your heart!
UTAGE: Wow.
SIGN: Just waking up
SIGN: Glasses
SIGN: At-home clothes
UTAGE: This is so much fun!
UTAGE: Personal desires... begone!
SIGN: Begone
TAMON: Thank you very much.
TAMON: Thanks to you, I was able to take
a selfie without throwing up.
UTAGE: Exactly what part of your face
would make you throw up?
UTAGE: I can understand your beauty throwing
the laws of physics out of whack, but...
TAMON: The fact that I'm taking selfies is gross.
TAMON: It doesn't really matter how my face looks.
UTAGE: But your face is important!
TAMON: My face is important.
UTAGE: I'll check them out as soon as they post them!
TAMON: You just saw me take them.
Wouldn't that be boring?
UTAGE: Absolutely not.
UTAGE: We just can't seem to agree
on anything, Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: I don't care what anyone else says.
Tamon-kun is the best in the world!
UTAGE: I will never let anyone say otherwise!
UTAGE: Make sure you eat the food
while it's still warm.
UTAGE: I'll be heading out for the day now.
TAMON: U-Um... Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: I think I'll somehow make it
to the Dome concert.
TAMON: Thank you so much
for everything you've done.
TAMON: Thanks to you,
SIGN: Fidget
TAMON: I feel like my mental state has gone from
excrement level to household waste level.
UTAGE: Who are you calling household waste?!
TAMON: "Tamon-kun is a national treasure."
UTAGE: It was nothing.
UTAGE: I just did my job. I didn't do
anything worthy of praise...
TAMON: That's not true.
TAMON: Idol work is a job, too.
But fans praise me all the time.
TAMON: And that... actually makes me really happy.
TAMON: I-I'm so sorry!
TAMON: Did I say something wrong again?
UTAGE: No.
UTAGE: It's just hearing you say that
UTAGE: as Gloomyhara-san rather than Tamon-kun
just got me all choked up.
TAMON: It's because you scolded me, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Say what now?
UTAGE: What? What?!
Lyrics: Supernova
Lyrics: It's a miracle that we
were born in the same era
Lyrics: So we've got to enjoy it
TAMON: I'm so sorry! I must be all slimy and gross.
UTAGE: You're not!
UTAGE: Please don't hide your smile!
It's such a waste!
TAMON: N-No! It's so gross!
TAMON: What an awkward smile.
TAMON: You're so cute.
FUJITA: Huh?
UTAGE: Oh.
FUJITA: Miss Housekeeper?!
FUJITA: If you're really a fan,
you need to know better!
UTAGE: I'm so sorry.
SIGN: Did nothing wrong
FUJITA: And Tamon!
FUJITA: I need you to be at least one billionth of
your stage persona even when you're at home!
UTAGE: I'm so sorry!
UTAGE: What am I even doing?
UTAGE: How could I let my desires take over and
push down a national treasure like that?!
UTAGE: What am I doing?!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: I'm not a Gloomyhara-san fan.
UTAGE: I'm a Tamon-kun fan. Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Oh...
UTAGE: this is bad.
SIGN: Tokyo Municipal Hanagatani High School
RIKO: Ugh, this is the worst.
SIGN: Idol Attacked by Stalker
RIKO: An idol got attacked by a stalker.
They barged into his home and tackled him.
RIKO: Ugh, this is the problem with these unicorns.
UTAGE: Yup, yup.
YUINA: The nerve of them barging into their
private lives when they're just a fan.
UTAGE: Yup, yup.
UTAGE: Ridiculous... more like re-die-culous, yup.
UTAGE: Yes, that's exactly right.
YUINA: More importantly, look!
YUINA: This month's issue's pin-ups of Tamon-kun!
YUINA: The amount of skin shown directly
correlates to the happiness index.
RIKO: I just can't.
UTAGE: Aw, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun, who's basically a zombie at home.
SIGN: Crumble
Crumble
RIKO: What's up, Utage?
RIKO: Is this the cause?
YUINA: This man is criminal.
UTAGE: What do I do? I can't forget him.
UTAGE: The next time I see him, I'm going
to become even more captivated.
UTAGE: I might... jump him again.
SIGN: Now, go forth on an adventure!
TAMON: Oh, Kinoshita-san!
TODA: Hello, it's been a while. It's me, Toda.
TODA: I'm thankfully out of the hospital now,
so I look forward to working with you again.
TODA: Oh, did you prefer the younger girl?
TODA: Oh, goodness!
Well, I'm going to get started.
UTAGE: I'm glad that Toda-san came back to work.
SIGN: Customer Recipe Notebook 15
SIGN: Customer No 35411
SIGN: Recipe Book for
SIGN: Fukuhara-sama
UTAGE: I'm going to go back
UTAGE: to being just another nameless fan.
F/ACE: EYES on you.
F/ACE: We are...
F/ACE: F/ACE!
TAMON: Performing at the Dome is just
the best! Am I right, Ouri?
OURI: Tamon-kun!
OURI: Come on. Don't waste your time on me.
OURI: The princess over there is calling out to you!
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: Ouri-kun
SIGN: Keito-kun
TAMON: Oh?
CROWD: Tamon! Ouri!
TAMON: Found her.
NATSUKI: Hey, no fair! You guys
shouldn't get a head start!
NATSUKI: Let me in on this, too!
OURI: Sure.
NATSUKI: Yay!
CROWD: Rintaro! Make me a heart!
CROWD: Thank you!
KEITO: Today's seriously been like a dream.
CROWD: Keito! I love you!
KEITO: Thank you all so much for coming to see us!
KEITO: To all my EYES out there!
KEITO: This next song is the last song
for the first half of our show!
KEITO: I'm going to embrace you all!
KEITO: Are you ready?!
FAN A: Take me!
FAN C: I'm not married, but I'd totally cheat on my
imaginary husband with you, Tamon-kun!
FAN B: I'm gonna die!
UTAGE: F/ACE is going to literally become
the face of our generation.
UTAGE: They are superstars.
Lyrics: In the dizzying endless flow of time,
Lyrics: We found each other amongst
the thousands of stars
Lyrics: We're shining star
Lyrics: The brightest star of all, the first star
Lyrics: Sparkling bright
Lyrics: Beautiful star
Lyrics: We're the new world's star
Lyrics: We'll show you things you've never seen
Lyrics: Let your voice reach over
Lyrics: I'll shine my light on you
Lyrics: My burning desire sparks a massive explosion
Lyrics: Supernova
Lyrics: Creating a new era beyond imagination
UTAGE: The fans are like rings that orbit
round and round around the stars.
Lyrics: Supernova
Lyrics: It's a miracle that we
were born in the same era
UTAGE: They're all just countless particles.
Lyrics: So we've got to enjoy it
(Yeah, song song song)
UTAGE: This is how far I should be from him.
Lyrics: Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
UTAGE: I can't make the mistake of becoming
a meteor and crash into him.
Lyrics: Harmonizing loud and proud
Lyrics: Song, song, song
UTAGE: You're so cool, Tamon-kun!
Lyrics: Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
Lyrics: Shining bright as one
SIGN: Church of Tamon
Lyrics: Supernova
UTAGE: Goodbye... Gloomyhara-san.
SIGN: Church of Tamon
UTAGE: I need to buy a drink
and hurry back to my seat.
UTAGE: Also, my emotions are a mess
from excitement and loneliness.
UTAGE: Huh? What?!
SIGN: No Unauthorized Entry
UTAGE: Huh? What is this literal piece of art
doing in front of me?
UTAGE: No, wait!
UTAGE: What are you doing here?!
TAMON: Well, I saw you in the crowd, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: He managed to spot me
in that huge sea of fans?
TAMON: I...
TAMON: I want to make the whole world smile,
but here you are crying.
TAMON: Does it have to do with why you stopped
coming to my place without saying anything?
UTAGE: O-Of course any fan would love
to know all about you, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: That obviously includes me.
UTAGE: That's exactly why
I shouldn't keep you to myself!
UTAGE: I might end up troubling you.
TAMON: I'll be the one that decides
if it's any trouble or not.
TAMON: So...
TAMON: don't say things like that!
TAMON: I need you by my side supporting me.
TAMON: I'm just hopeless without you.
UTAGE: I can't. I can't say no.
UTAGE: Okay...
TAMON: My face...! My face hurts!
UTAGE: Now's not the time
to switch out of work mode!
UTAGE OVERLAP: To all of the Tamon-kun fans across Japan...
UTAGE: You still have the second half
of the show! You need to go!
TAMON: Okay!
UTAGE OVERLAP: I'm so sorry.
UTAGE OVERLAP: I'm here to support you!
SIGN: No Unauthorized Entry
UTAGE: I am going to live my life as a bad fan.
UTAGE: Sincerely, Utage.
TAMON: We're not letting the party stop just yet!
TAMON: I'm not letting you guys sleep tonight!
TAMON: This is our next song...
TAMON: "Sweet Magic"!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!